<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Julian Fortune</title>
    <link>https://julianfortune.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Julian Fortune</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://julianfortune.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Speech Workload Estimation for Intelligent Human-Machine Systems</title>
      <link>https://julianfortune.com/publications/hfes2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianfortune.com/publications/hfes2020/</guid>
      <description>Julian Fortune, Dr. Jamison Heard, and Dr. Julie A. Adams Accepted to the Human Factors and Ergonomics Society Annual Meeting.
Abstract Demanding task environments (e.g., supervising a remotely piloted aircraft) require performing tasks quickly and accurately; however, periods of low and high operator workload can decrease task performance. Intelligent modulation of the system’s demands and interaction modality in response to changes in operator workload state may increase performance by avoiding undesirable workload states.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper ECG</title>
      <link>https://julianfortune.com/projects/paperecg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianfortune.com/projects/paperecg/</guid>
      <description>The Paper ECG interface   This application provides tools for cardiology professionals to digitize digital scans or images of ECG print outs, and is the first free and open source application to provide such functionality. Users can annotate regions of the image to extra signal data and specify the scale information to create an accurate digitization of the signals. The digitization processes are implementations of peer-reviewed ECG signal digitization algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unjumble</title>
      <link>https://julianfortune.com/projects/unjumble/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianfortune.com/projects/unjumble/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Witchcraft</title>
      <link>https://julianfortune.com/projects/witchcraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianfortune.com/projects/witchcraft/</guid>
      <description>Witchcraft&amp;rsquo;s interface   A fully equipped software synthesizer built with Max/MSP. Includes 2 wavetable synthesizes which allow drawing waveforms directly on the interface. Both wavetables come with FM controllers. Also includes 2 basic oscillators, a physical modeling oscillator, a harmonic oscillator and 2 noise sources. The generators and the filters are laid out to intuitively show the signal flow. At the bottom are the modulators and effects are along the side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://julianfortune.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianfortune.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Education I am currently completing my final year at Oregon State University. My major is Computer Science, and I am specializing in artificial intelligence and machine learning.
Experience I built front-end features utilized by all LucidChart customers with Typescript and Angular, and expanded back-end models in Scala during my internship at Lucid Software during the Summer of 2020. From June 2018 to June 2019 I interned at CBT Nuggets, working on the iOS, tvOS, and UWP platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Speech Workload Estimation</title>
      <link>https://julianfortune.com/publications/honorsthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianfortune.com/publications/honorsthesis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAHRTA: A Supervisory-Based Adaptive Human-Robot Teaming Architecture</title>
      <link>https://julianfortune.com/publications/sahrta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianfortune.com/publications/sahrta/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speech Workload Estimation for Human-Machine Interaction</title>
      <link>https://julianfortune.com/publications/hfes2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianfortune.com/publications/hfes2019/</guid>
      <description>Julian Fortune, Dr. Jamison Heard, and Dr. Julie A. Adams Abstract Performing tasks quickly and accurately in dynamic and intense environments is critical, such as supervising a remotely piloted aircraft; however, these environments contain periods of low and high workload, which can decrease task performance. A system capable of intelligently adapting its interaction modality based on the human’s workload state may mitigate these undesirable workload states: underload and overload. Such a system requires mechanisms to determine accurately the human’s overall workload state and each workload component state (i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
